https://sabiansymbols.com/privacy-policy/

Login
Username
Password
Remember Me
Forget your password?
Username or E-mail
Remembered Password?
Privacy Policy & Website Terms of Use
We value the privacy of our subscribers, website members and clients. We use the information they have provided to personalise their experience on our site and provide them with newsletters, blog updates and information about new or upgraded products.
We will never share subscriber or client details with third parties. Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason without your consent, other than for the purposes of delivering purchased products.
If subscribers or clients need or wish to modify any of their information, including unsubscribing from any mail lists, they can update by contacting us or clicking in the unsubscribe link in an email. Please keep your contact details up to date when you change emails so you can keep receiving newsletters and information from us. You can unsubscribe at any time.
Privacy Policy
Sabian Symbols by Lynda Hill
This Privacy Policy sets out our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information that we collect through this website https://sabiansymbols.com (Site) or directly from you. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Please contact us if you have any questions.
You providing us with personal information indicates that you have had sufficient opportunity to access this Privacy Policy and that you have read and accepted it. If you do not wish to provide personal information to us, then you do not have to do so, however it may affect your use of this Site or any products and services offered on it.
1. Type of personal information collected
Personal Information: The type of personal information we collect may include is set out on our website.
If we receive your personal information from third parties, we will protect it as set out in this Privacy Policy.
2. Collection and use of personal information
We collect and use the personal information for purposes including to contact and communicate with you, for internal record keeping and for marketing.
3. Disclosure of personal information
We may disclose personal information for purposes including to provide our products and services to you, and as required by law.
Where we disclose your personal information to third parties for these purposes, we will request that the third party follow this Privacy Policy regarding handling of your personal information.
4. Access to and correction of personal information
Access: You may request details of personal information that we hold about you, in certain circumstances set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). An administrative fee may be payable for the provision of information. We may refuse to provide you with information that we hold about you, in certain circumstances set out in the Privacy Act.
Correction: If you believe that any information we hold on you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please contact us by email. We rely in part upon customers advising us when their personal information changes. We will respond to any request within a reasonable time. We will endeavour to promptly correct any information found to be inaccurate, incomplete or out of date.
5. Complaints about breach
If you believe that we have breached the Australian Privacy Principles and wish to make a complaint about that breach, please contact us on the email address below.
6. Unsubscribe
To unsubscribe from our e-mail database, or opt out of communications, please contact us at the details below.
7. Storage and Security
We are committed to ensuring that the information you provide is secure.null
Cookie Use
This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your
machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general,
cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for
things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to
third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will
make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable
cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this
is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help
section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website
which offers guidance for all modern browsers
Website Terms of Use
Welcome to our website. This website with URL address https://sabiansymbols.com is owned and operated by  Sabian Symbols by Lynda Hill. Should you continue to use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern  Sabian Symbols by Lynda Hill’s relationship with you in connection with this website. Should you not agree with any of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.
The term ‘ Sabian Symbols by Lynda Hill’ or ‘us’ or ‘our’ or ‘we’ refers to  Sabian Symbols by Lynda Hill, the owner of the website, whose registered office is in New South Wales. The term ‘you’ or ‘your’ refers to the website user.
Your use of this website is subject to the following terms and conditions:
The content of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without prior notice.This website uses cookies to monitor browsing preferences. If you allow cookies to be used, the following personal information may be stored by us for use by third parties: Name, address, business name, phone number, email address, business information.Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the performance, accuracy, timeliness, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You hereby acknowledge that such information and materials may contain mistakes, inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude any liability for such to the fullest extent permissible by law.Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the content, design, layout, appearance, look and graphics of the website. Any reproduction of the website’s material is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to us, are acknowledged on the website.Unauthorised use of this website may be a criminal offence and/or give rise to a claim for damages.This website may also, on occasion, include links to other websites which are not controlled by us. These links are provided for your convenience to provide you with further information. You acknowledge that they are used at your own risk. They do not signify that we recommend or endorse the websites. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those websites.Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of your use of it is subject to the laws of New South Wales.You may only use the website for lawful purposes and in a manner consistent with the nature and purpose of the website.These terms and conditions do not relate to your use of any product or service described on our website unless otherwise agreed. You must refer to the individual warranty relevant to any particular product or service.These terms and conditions may be amended from time to time. Your continued use of our website following any such amendments will be deemed to be confirmation that you accept those amendments.You indemnify us from and against all claims, suits, demands, actions, liabilities, costs and expenses (including legal costs and expenses on a full indemnity basis) resulting from your use of the website.In no event will we be liable for any loss, damage, cost or expense including legal costs and expenses (whether direct or indirect) incurred by you in connection with the use of this website.Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, we take no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
Last update: 16 March 2019
For any questions or notice, please contact us at:
Sabian Symbols by Lynda Hill
Email: lyndahill[at]gmail[dot]com
These policies are provided FREE by legalvision.com.au
This website is dedicated to sharing the magic of the Sabian Symbols, a unique set of images to chart your destiny based on the zodiac. Join Lynda Hill and a community of spiritual seekers, astrologers and students who tune in to the Symbols every day.
ABOUT
Lynda Hill
Sabian Symbols
Support the Symbols
PRODUCTS & SERVICES
Books and Cards
Readings
Donate & Support
